moviehustle.com 2017-11-30

# Privacy Policy

We want you to do so feeling secure that we will not spam you share or otherwise distribute your personal information. 

What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?

When contacting on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience. 

When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you enter information on our site.

We receive information from you from http://moviehustle.com

How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you contacting us or giving us any suggestion to improve our work.

How do we protect your information?

Movie Hustle has its own information protection mechanisms in place. We use regular Malware Scanning. We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

Do we use 'cookies'?

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

###   
THIRD-PARTY DISCLOSURE

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

Third-party links

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

Google

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.

We have implemented the following:

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.  
 **CONTACTING US**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

admin@moviehustle.com
